!صوفي تقود
!نحن نقود
What about these shots of the weather here ?
!صوفي ، ماء مجاني
!ساعد نفسك
In georgia you can drink any water due to it's filtration system here
Now , we are going to city called "Bottema"
this city in front of the sea and the people can pass the boundary to Turkey
in front of Black sea , we will driving to it and it takes 3 hours, i will show you the car that we rent
NEW CAR !!
we rent this car for 2 days , 40$ per day
!بنروح نسبح
حقا ً ؟
!!أجل ، وقت الصيف
صوفي تايم
ان كانت اول مرة تسمعوها فهي دائماً تردد هذه الكلمة في قناتها
ok guys (in Arabic)
سوف تكون مقدمتك
..صوتوا يا شباب
سأضع تصويت هنا أو هناك يا شباب
تريدين بعض الشيبس؟
!إنّه رائع
!لا ، هذا ليس شيبس
هل تعرفين ماهذا ؟
!أجل
صوفي ، هذا الطعام لكِ
لأنّك قطة كيوت
!وهذا لك
أنا كلب ؟
Ok now we are going to bottema !
Before we start please give us the support with 50k likes guys
we try to reach it guys and have a nice day !
" إلى مدينة " باتومي
!يا إلهي خمس ساعات
كاميراتي الجديدة هنا
لا
انها ثقيلةٌ جداً كيف يمكنك حملها
مريبٌ جداً
مع ثلاثة أيدي
ثلاثة أيدي ؟
أريد طبق من الفاكهة
تلك الزبادي
زبادي ؟
we arrived to bottema guys and we expect it will be 3 or 4 hours but
it takes more than 7 hours imagine !
We were deceived in this way
the most important thing is my coffe
we will take some shots in one city and leave
i saw something like that city before in Amman (Jordan)
Tourist city close to sea
صوفي انصدمت
!لا يمكن
just shock !
هل هذا حقيقي؟
للغداء  ؟
Now we will walk in a very old place called "Boulevard " since 1884* been there i think !
I can't believe park inside the building ?
!فكرة خرافية
هل يمكنني ؟
لا ؟
!لا
!إنّها مجردّ طفلة
في ستوري الانتستقرام الناس تقولي لازم تسبح
هل سألتهم ؟
أجل
!اذاً هيا بنا
Guys what do you think about this idea it's working on Youtube nowadays ..
which is insta story control our way like i can control Sophie way or vise versa
If this video reach 50k like we will make it in Jordan together !
imagine (in arabic)
look at this on the streets
tennis table and billiard and i find Sophie here are playing too !
!آسفه للغاية
we will rent this motor
have two seats on it
مستعده ؟
here you can rent anything you want
This building is so great !
تريدين القيادة ؟
!أجل
!لا ، أنا فقط
!هيا بنا هيا
!صوفي ستقوم بالقيادة
!حظاً موفقاً
!صوفي تقود
!أجل
How was my Drone shots ?
Finally we find it , after we travel in many countries around the world !
The best MacDonald In the planet !
You can see this building !
The best MacDonald In the plante , look !
Here is outside seats
the best MacDonald in the planet !
!إنّه حقاً رائع
نحن من اوكرانيا
هل لديكم ماكلونالز مثل هذا في اوكرانيا ؟
!لا
you can see it guys the hole building made of glass !
here you can order from your car (Drive-Thru)
Guys look at my Drone !
i will change it soon
اعملوا شير لهذا الفيديو حتى اجمع ثمنه
so i can buy a new one if you make like and share !